getfreshwithafriend.com 2011-12-24

# Privacy Policy

## Kimberly-Clark Privacy Policy

This Web site is owned and operated by Kimberly-Clark Corporation. Here at Kimberly-Clark, we recognize that many visitors to our site are concerned about the information they provide and how we treat that information. Our Privacy Policy addresses those concerns. We may update the Policy from time to time, so please check in occasionally. Regulations enacted in April 2000 under the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act give children under 13 years of age greater privacy protection online. Please see our policy under "Children" below.

### Our Policy

At our site, we don't collect personally identifiable information from you unless you provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. You can visit our sites without telling us who you are or revealing information about yourself. However, if you specifically agree to provide us with identifiable information, such as by asking to be put on our mailing list, we may contact you from time to time.

There are some features of our site that require you to sign up to use. And if you do sign up, we use the information you supply for the purpose of providing the products, product information or services you request. Because of the volume of requests we receive, however, we may have to give your name, e-mail and postal addresses to a fulfillment house or distributor of our products who partners with us. On our behalf our partners will provide you with the information or products in which you expressed an interest. Our partners have agreed to keep the personal information they receive from us confidential and secure unless you have given your consent to its being shared with other product manufacturers.

Our site sometimes includes notices of sweepstakes or other promotions we are conducting, and we may permit you to send your entry electronically in some cases. If that occurs, we will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion (i.e., to contact you if you're a winner).

### Children

Children's privacy is of primary concern to us, and our Policy and practices reflect applicable laws and regulations on children's privacy. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. Any communication we get that is identified as being from a child under 13 will not be kept by Kimberly-Clark.

### Cookies

Like many companies, we sometimes use "cookie" technology on our Web site. These cookies are stored on your computer by your browser. When you log in, this type of cookie tells us whether you've visited us before or are a new visitor. The cookie doesn't obtain any personal information about you or provide us with any way to contact you, and the cookie doesn't extract any information from your computer. We do use the cookie to help us identify site features in which you have the greatest interest, so that we can provide more of what you may want.

We use the services of NetIQ/WebTrends to track the paths our customers take through our site. In doing so, we are better able to see where our customers go within our site and ensure our site is easy to navigate. If you have any questions concerning NetIQ/WebTrends, you should refer to the [NetIQ/WebTrends Reporting Service Privacy Policy](http://ondemand.webtrends.com/privacypolicy.asp) to learn how they collect and use information, particularly the section of the Policy on Privacy Statement for Visitors to Sites Tracked by WebTrends on Demand.

GIF files are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our Web site. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to the [DoubleClick Privacy Policy](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx).

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us via e-mail or phone us at 1-800-665-9773. For postal mail, please write to us at:

Kimberly-Clark Corporation  
P.O. Box 2020  
Neenah, WI 54957-2020
